Finding Aid for the Kay Sugahara Papers LSC.2354
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Series 3: Personal files, 1928-1988
  - Sunbelt Dixie photo album, 1977-1978 (Box 167, Folder 1)
  - Jolly Sprite photo album, 1986 (Box 168, Folder 1)
  - Atlas Rex photo album, 1984 (Box 169, Folder 1)
  - Orient and Ocean Rex photo album, 1985 (Box 169, Folder 2)
  - 36 Ship launch CD-Rs and DVDs, 1974-2007 (Box 170, Folder 1)
  - Six ship launch VHS tapes, 1980s (Box 171, Folder 1)
  - Twelve FML DVDS - tapes and Fairfield Vietnam opening, undated (Box 171, Folder 2)
  - Nineteen FML DVDs, undated (Box 172, Folder 1)
  - Yone K. High school yearbook scrapbook, 1926 (Box 173, Folder 1)
  - Rolled photographs - Fumi K., undated (Box 174, Folder 1)
  - Yone K. dance cards, 1930 (Box 174, Folder 2)
  - Yone K. and Fumi K. rolled photos, 1915-1920s (Box 175, Folder 1)
  - 26 FML 50th Anniversary DVCPRO tapes, 2007 (Box 176, Folder 1)
  - 6 FML MiniDVs, undated (Box 176, Folder 2)
  - 26 FML 50th Anniversary DVCPRO tapes, 2007 (Box 177, Folder 1)
  - 1 Edit rushes - Usoki & Nagasaki DVCAM, undated (Box 177, Folder 2)
  - 29 FML 50th Anniversary DVCPRO tapes, 2007 (Box 178, Folder 1)
  - 20 FML 50th Anniversary DVCPRO tapes, 2007 (Box 179, Folder 1)
  - 4 FML DVDs, 2007 June (Box 179, Folder 2)
  - 2 FML ISO CD-ROMs, undated (Box 179, Folder 3)
  - Framed photos of Yone, her family, and KS, 1916, 1930s, 1973 (Box 180, Folder 1-5)
  - Photocopies of photos, undated (Box 181, Folder 1)
  - Sugahara family in Sendai photo album, 1987 November 3-15 (Box 181, Folder 2)
  - Photos from SSK, undated (Box 181, Folder 3)
  - Brochures of FML & affiliated companies, 1979-1995 (Box 181, Folder 4)
  - Loyalty's Janus Face, 2012 (Box 181, Folder 5)
  - Shimbun 1, 2014 (Box 181, Folder 6)
  - Fairchem Filly small photo album, 2007 January 26 (Box 181, Folder 7)
  - Fairchem Charger launch photos, 2008 December 8 (Box 181, Folder 8)
  - Fairchem Steed launch photos, 2005 May 11 (Box 181, Folder 9)
  - 277 Park Avenue office photos, 1972 March 24 (Box 181, Folder 10)
  - KS in Japan scrapbook, 1980s (Box 181, Folder 11)
  - FML documentary binder, undated (Box 181, Folder 12-14)
  - Kamekichi S. funeral photo & KGS playing in a fountain photo, 1922, 1938 (Box 182, Folder 1)
  - Sugahara family photo album, 1940s-2000s (Box 182, Folder 2)
  - Pres. Carter w KS, KGS, 1980 October 3 (Box 182, Folder 3)
  - Ken Walsh photo album, undated (Box 182, Folder 4)
  - KGS photos and documents, 1990s-2000s (Box 182, Folder 5)
  - KKS USAI Man of the Year photos, 1988 (Box 182, Folder 6)
  - Mounted Kamekichi S. funeral photo, 1922 March 22 (Box 182, Folder 7)
  - Sugahara family photos, 1940s-1990s (Box 182, Folder 8)
  - FML 50th Anniversary photo album, 2007 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Quotes letters, 1929-1951 (Box 184, Folder 1-10)
  - Business project folder, 1938-1944 (Box 184, Folder 11-19)
  - KS & YS letters, 1927-1933 (Box 184, Folder 20-36)
  - Handwritten letters, 1933-1943 (Box 185, Folder 1-25)
  - Caucasian correspondence, 1942-1943 (Box 186, Folder 1-2)
  - Quotes letters, 1951-1987 (Box 186, Folder 3)
  - Handwritten letters, 1944 (Box 186, Folder 4-17)
  - KS & YS letters, 1944 (Box 186, Folder 18-28)
  - Handwritten letters, 1944 (Box 186, Folder 29-30)
  - Handwritten letters, 1944-1945 (Box 187, Folder 1-13)
  - KS & YS letters, 1945 (Box 187, Folder 14-21)
  - Handwritten letters, 1944-1945 (Box 187, Folder 22-28)
  - Letters and OSS travel documents, 1945 (Box 188, Folder 1)
  - Letters, 1945 (Box 188, Folder 2-3)
  - KS & YS letters, 1945 (Box 188, Folder 4-7)
  - Envelopes, 1945 (Box 188, Folder 8-15)
  - Fairfield Vietnam framed photograph, undated (Box 188, Folder 16)
  - Fairfield Chemical Carriers flag and Fairfield Vietnam brochure, undated (Box 188, Folder 17)
  - FML photos, undated (Box 188, Folder 18)
  - Oversized letters, 1929-1951, 1980-1993 (Box 189, Folder 1-19)
  - Kay unanswered correspondence, 1940s (Box 189, Folder 24)
  - Letters and ephemera, 1942-1946 (Box 190, Folder 1-21)
  - KS & YS letters, 1946-1951 (Box 190, Folder 22-24)
  - Handwritten letters, 1947-1949 (Box 191, Folder 1-4)
  - Draft and time cards, 1941-1943 (Box 191, Folder 5)
  - News clippings, 1940s-1950s (Box 191, Folder 6)
  - Letters, 1947-1952 (Box 191, Folder 7-23)
  - Ephemera, 1940s, 1956 (Box 191, Folder 24)
  - Letters and photocopies of photos, 1980-1985 (Box 191, Folder 25)
  - Sugahara family tree, 1987-1993 (Box 192, Folder 1)
  - KS professorship announcement, 2012 April (Box 192, Folder 2)
  - UCLA, 1972-1979 (Box 195, Folder 13)
  - KS taxes, 1975-1976 (Box 197, Folder 2)
  - KS photographs, 1980s (Box 201, Folder 5-8)
  - Tsaji party VHS, 1986 October 3; yrlsc_2354_202_001; 1 Video Recordings (1 VHS; Duration: 0:36:50) (Box 202, Case 1)
    CONTAINS AUDIOVISUAL MATERIALS: Audiovisual materials are available for access. All requests to access digital materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
  - Japan Reaches for the 21st Century VHS, 1986 (Box 202, Folder 2)
  - 8 Kleiner audiocassettes, 1987 (Box 202, Folder 3)
  - 4 Howard Schonberger audiocassettes, 1987 (Box 202, Folder 4)
  - Howard Schonberger KS tapes translation, undated (Box 202, Folder 5)
  - One AMC audiocassette, 1986 (Box 202, Folder 6)
  - One KS Tokyo audiocassette, 1985 (Box 202, Folder 7)
  - Two unmarked audiocassettes, undated (Box 202, Folder 8)
  - Komatsu and Hill correspondence, 1953, 1957 (Box 203, Folder 1)
  - Photographs, 1970s-1980s (Box 203, Folder 2-5)
  - KS letters, 1931-1941 (Box 204, Folder 1)
  - KS ephemera, 1927-1930s (Box 204, Folder 2)
  - KS diary, 1929-1931 (Box 204, Folder 3)
  - Yone Sugahara educational materials, 1930-1950s (Box 204, Folder 4)
  - KS radio addresses, 1937 (Box 204, Folder 5)
  - BMS/BTS birth-labor records, 1945 (Box 204, Folder 6)
  - Occupational Survey, 1942 July (Box 204, Folder 7)
  - Camouflage Survey, 1942 (Box 204, Folder 8)
  - KS personal correspondence - Granada era, 1940s (Box 204, Folder 9-11)
  - Inter center correspondence, 1942 (Box 204, Folder 12)
  - KS - Amache loyalty applications, 1943 (Box 204, Folder 13)
  - KS - Amache publications, 1943 (Box 204, Folder 14)
  - Evacuee Attitudes, 1943 (Box 204, Folder 15)
  - Yone Granada souvenirs, 1942-1945 (Box 204, Folder 16)
  - Yone Granada souvenirs, 1942-1945 (Box 205, Folder 1)
  - OSS Marigold Project, 1945 (Box 205, Folder 2)
  - E. Dooman Bio, 1950 (Box 205, Folder 3)
  - KS letters, 1947 January (Box 205, Folder 4)
  - ACJ/M Kleiman, 1946, 1949 (Box 205, Folder 5)
  - Newsweek article on FEC 230, 1947 (Box 205, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1950 (Box 205, Folder 7)
  - Letters, 1951-1976 (Box 205, Folder 8-12)
  - Hatsuse Kuwahara obituary, 1978 (Box 205, Folder 13)
  - YS personal, 1994 (Box 205, Folder 14)
  - Playboy Japan KS interview, 1984 May (Box 205, Folder 15)
  - Sugahara-Kuwahara history, 1983-1995 (Box 205, Folder 16)
  - Cherry Tree donation, 1986 (Box 205, Folder 17)
  - JA internment articles, 1981-1987 (Box 205, Folder 18)
  - Sendai reunion, 1987 (Box 205, Folder 19)
  - KS condolences, 1988 (Box 205, Folder 20-21)
  - Kay Sugahara Story FML photo album, undated (Box 206, Folder 1)
  - KS historic Japan photos, 1950s (Box 206, Folder 2)
  - Kay Sugahara Story FML photo album, undated (Box 207, Folder 1)
  - Key to the City of Los Angeles, 1981-1983 (Box 208, Folder 1)